hkexpress.com 2019-05-31

# HK Express - Legal & Privacy

Hong Kong Express Airways Limited ("Our Company") respects the privacy of the information provided by users and will endeavor to ensure that proper protection is given to such information.

Our Company pledges to meet, and where possible exceed, internationally recognized standards of data privacy protection, in complying with the law of confidence and/or the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, whichever is applicable. In doing so, Our Company will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.

### Corporate/Personal Information:

When you use our web site, Our Company may request you to provide us with your corporate/personal data from time to time, including but not limited to:

  * Your personal information such as your name, gender, date of birth, passport or other personally identifiable number and information about your registered status with any of our subsidiaries, associated companies and/or business associates;
  * Your contact information such as your telephone numbers, mailing addresses, email addresses, and fax numbers;
  * Your credit or debit card information and billing information, including name of cardholder, card number, billing address and expiry date;
  * Your business information such as company name, business title and associated contact information;
  * Your travel details such as flight information, travel companions’ personal information, destination contact information, seat and meal preferences, flight and hotel preferences, and information related to traveler special needs;
  * Your responses to market surveys and contests conducted by us or on our behalf.

### Methods in Collecting Corporate/Personal Data:

  * The input of figures for all calculations;
  * Enquiry forms and information provided by you in your enquiry;
  * Messages by you in our web site;
  * Questionnaire submitted by you;
  * The email between you and Our Company;
  * Your activity record of our website;
  * Cookies files to store and track your information without your notice;
  * Any other means as reasonably accessible to Our Company from time to time.

### Purposes for Collection of Corporate/Personal Data:

  * To compile the general statistical database of our web site, for instance, number of browsers, time of visits, occupation and gender distribution of visitors and members.
  * The introduction or supply of suitable products and service in accordance with your interest and habits.
  * The delivery of products and service information requested by you.
  * The collection of identity documentation number for the purpose of verification.
  * To facilitate Our Company to verify and follow up any matters and questions (including but not limited to overdue payments) in respect of any account maintained by yourself with Our Company (and/or with any of Our Company's holding company, subsidiaries and associates). For this purpose, you hereby authorize Our Company to furnish, transfer and disclose all or any of your corporate/personal data to any party(ies) to follow up and settle the said matters and questions.
  * To facilitate the implementation of any activities or services to be co-organized by Our Company and our business partners.
  * To facilitate Our Company to design and provide you with better and more tailored-made services and to facilitate Our Company to develop and promote the business of Our Company.

### Guidelines for disclosure of Corporate/ Personal Data to Third Parties:

The corporate/personal data collected by Our Company, Our Company's holding company, subsidiaries and associates would be exchanged when required to perform any of the aforesaid purposes for collection of corporate/personal data and other matters and arrangements which can facilitate the said performance;

The companies and contractors who provide services to Our Company may obtain corporate/personal data collected by Our Company to perform any of the aforesaid purposes for collection of corporate/personal data and other matters and arrangements which can facilitate the said performance. These data will only be protected by their own corporate/personal data (protection of privacy) rules. However, Our Company will use our best endeavor to keep the collected corporate/personal data confidential.

When you activate any link and access to websites operated by others from Our Company's website, any of your corporate/personal data released and/or obtained by others at the said other link and websites will not be under the protection of our Privacy Policy.

Clients' identifiable information will not be disclosed to our advertisers. But, Our Company will deliver notice and email to targeted advertising audience to provide statistical data of our web site to them.

In activities or services co-organized by Our Company and our business partners, shared information will include the corporate/personal records which are necessary for the implementation of such activities and services.

To perform any of the aforesaid purposes for collection of corporate/personal data and other matters and arrangements which can facilitate the said performance and/or to facilitate any due diligence exercise in respect of any potential acquisition/merger transaction(s) involving Our Company, Our Company is entitled to furnish, transfer and disclose any of your corporate/personal data obtained as aforesaid to any person to Our Company, including but not limited to, our group of companies such as reward-U (HK) Limited; any agent, contractor or third party service provider who provides administrative, marketing and research, distribution, data processing, telemarketing, telecommunications, computer, payment or other services to us in connection with the operation of its business; other business associates such air carriers, land or sea transport operators, loyalty program operators and other companies involved in providing customer service or fulfilling customer requests; credit reference agencies; credit, debit and /or charge card companies and/or banks; government or non-government authorities, agencies and/or regulators; medical professionals, insurers and clinics/hospitals.

Our Company will use our best endeavor to keep the collected corporate/personal data confidential.

### Other Information Collectors

Except as otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy governs and addresses only the use and disclosure of the information we collect from you. As far as the information that you disclose to other parties, including but not limited to the advertisers, business partners and our strategic alliances on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, is concerned, different rules and policies shall apply to their respective use or disclosure of your information. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they have their own privacy customs and policies. Since Our Company and/or its other related companies do not have control of the privacy policies of third parties, your information disclosed to them is subject to their privacy customs and policies. It is thus advisable for you to ensure that you understand the effect of the privacy customs and policies of other third parties before you disclose your corporate/personal information to them.

While we strive to protect your corporate/personal information, Our Company and/or its other related companies cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In addition, third party Internet sites and other third party's services accessible through our sites or other parties which are collecting data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, etc., have separate and independent privacy and data collection practices. Under no circumstances should Our Company and/or its other related companies be held responsible and liable for these other and independent policies, actions and/or any loss, damages and claim that you may suffer in relation thereto. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

You may request access to and correct your Personal Data held by us.  If you wish to obtain a copy of any of your Personal Data, if you believe that the Personal Data relating to you which we collect and maintain is incorrect, or if you believe that the Personal Data held by us was used beyond the scope of the purpose of use disclosed above or was acquired by fraudulent or unlawful means or provided to a third party without your prior consent, please write to us at the address below.

A request for access or correction to, or deletion of Personal Data or for information regarding policies and practices and kinds of Personal Data held by us must be in writing and sent to us via postal mail at the following address:

The Data Protection Officer  
Hong Kong Express Airways Limited  
7th Floor, One Citygate,  
20 Tat Tung Road, Tung Chung, Lantau, Hong Kong

We may charge a reasonable fee for the processing of any data access request.

Our Company reserves the right to amend our Privacy Policy to enable your corporate/personal data to be fully protected.
